hi Bashar and you good
day um couple years ago in one of the
Transmissions you responded to a
question about gravity with the copper
ball experiment yes in the copper ball
experiment it was a demonstration of
this notion that location is a property
of every object
correct I've been thinking about that
every day since oh all right and I want
to talk about some ideas that came out
of it by all means but first I want
review The Experiment so that all of us
can do this together is that is that all
right yes the experiment is this idea
many of you already understand how our
ships travel from star to star because
we treat the idea of location as not a
place an object exists in but as an
actual equational vibrational property
of the object so that an object existing
here and then existing here are actually
literally two different objects because
when you change the location variable in
the object here and impose upon it the
idea of the energy of the locational
variable of this location the object
must by definition cease to exist here
and immediately and instantly exist here
and thus no travel in the intervening
distance has actually occurred the
object has simply popped out of one
reality and popped back into the reality
somewhere else based on the new
locational variable that you have
injected into into its overall
vibrational signature equation so the
experiment to begin to practice this to
learn this principle is to have a very
very flat table very flat as flat as you
can get it and at least six to 10 of
your feet long and have a very very thin
as round as you can make it thin copper
sphere then you have the ability to
extract from that sphere either by
striking it or through some other
methodology the actual tone the
signature frequency of that pure very
thin shelled copper sphere that is
hollow when you extract the tone that is
the signature frequency of that sphere
and then move the sphere to the other
end of the table and extract the tone
from the sphere there location B then
move the sphere back to location a then
in any way you can with your technology
either acoustically or electronically
and simplify and magnify the vibrational
tone of location B but bombard the
sphere in location a with the
vibrational tone of location B and you
will begin to watch that the sphere will
start to roll to location B
automatically with that vibrational tone
and once it arrives in that location
will stop and go no further because it
has found its resting Point within that
vibrational equation that's the
experiment fascinating that will begin
the ability to investigate how to really
unlock an object from one vibrational
locational reality and in that unlocked
State impose upon it enough energy of
the new location to have it actually pop
out from location a and pop in at
location B without actually just
traveling from one point to the other
make sense yeah yes all right what
really stuck out with me was the idea
that it traveled slowly and I I made me
wonder about gravity and general
yes if first of all there's two things
that emerg from this experiment number
one if a vibration can be detected it
must be radiating from every object of
course that means that the location of
all objects in the universe radiate
their location of course that's how we
create the navigational charts that our
ships use to go from place to place
because once you understand the Matrix
of locational vibrations in a relatively
limited area it's relatively easy to
extrapolate that out to the rest of the
universe right I assume there's a
graduation of frequency that relates to
location yes sense it's turning the
entire universe into the understanding
of a real stat right the other the
emerging idea that comes to experiment
is that objects will take on frequency
and thus move to the location
representative of that frequency yes
because it's representative of that
object in that location I understand
isn't that exactly what gravity does I
mean right now our scientists talk about
gravity in terms of warping space and
thus object in a sense from one
perspective that isn't incorrect but
it's not the whole picture you're still
seeing just the side effect of the
relationship of frequencies with each
other and the relationship of geometry
with itself in certain
patterns like let's take a mass full
object like a a neutron star highly
dense collection of matter yes it has a
highly coherent gravity wave radiation
because there's a lot of matter in one
area yeah that radiates out and any
object in its vicinity takes on that
frequency and and as such it it's drawn
in yes so that's the mechanism of
gravity isn't it yes that's it
reidentifying the locational variables
within objects because it is powerful
enough to do so right it's powerful
enough to overwhelm the idea of their
initial locational signature and the
objects Sur like a Sun or a star or
whatever yes they also take up the
vibrations of those around them and they
wobble around a little bit so it's
interactive exchange yes fundamentally
it is an exchange of information that's
what gravity
is I knew
it well congratulations been thinking
about this every
day and now there's another component I
mean we also have this concept we've
seen called time dilation frame dragging
objects that rotate planets have well
that's very simply explained it's part
of the vibrational elemination is
temporal isn't it there's a temporal
comp well yes but time is a side effect
but if you want to really look at it in
the simplistic way the most simplistic
way possible since you already know it's
just SpaceTime it's one thing that has
Expressions as space and expressions as
time yes right so just look at SpaceTime
as the 100% thing look at it as a
sliding
scale if you're at this end you're
experiencing shall we say less space and
more time because you're not
moving you understand yeah but if you go
to this end you're experiencing the idea
of less time because you're occupying
more of the space
by moving so anytime you move you're
using up the space component and not
leaving enough room for the time
component and therefore time seems to
slow down because the whole picture of
SpaceTime has to always equal 100% so if
you're occupying space 50% time has to
slow down 50% because there's no room
for it to be moving at 51% if you're
occupying 50% of the Space by movement
mhm so it's really totally just a 100
100% thing and depending upon where you
are in the sliding scale determines how
fast or slow or how much you experience
of space and
time does that make sense it does let's
have a little fun with this oh all right
I thought we were having fun but go
ahead let's have some more fun we talked
about some things coming up and I want
to open the door to that terms of
Technology yeah if we were able to
detect gravity waves I don't I know we
can't really quite do that actually you
already have the high frequency gravity
waves is that what it is your scientists
have recently conducted an experiment
where they have for the first time
confirmed the existence of gravity waves
yeah one of my clients is working on
that yes well so are many others yeah um
the problem is we don't really have the
detect well we can't detect it outside
of the background noise so there's a
discrimination problem right now we
understand but that's a challenge that
you will have fun solving yeah it's
deliriously fun
um well is
convincing I want to just put out a a
proposal for a electrogravitic
propulsion system yes if we could detect
gravity waves say a forward area of a of
a ship yes relay that data to the center
of mass of the ship amplify it modulate
it yes and part it to a center of mass
wouldn't that result in forward movement
along the vector described by the as
long as you also impart the idea of less
behind the ship so that you're riding
away wave like a surfer again scientists
are already working on this on your
planet yeah okay so that would work oh
yes absolutely your scientists already
understand at least some of them do the
true beginnings of what you have
colloquially referred to as a warp drive
you just don't quite have the technology
for it yet but the principle is
sound what is the nature of these ways
what what would be the best way to start
really detecting them with with
assuredness really well as soon as you
understand that the relationship within
gravity is an informational exchange and
that a locational variable is part of
that then you will begin to understand
how to use gravity and how to alter the
information in a way that serves you is
it an electromagnetic I mean you talked
about vibration well electrogravitic if
you wish to put it that way the other
thing I I'm intuitively sensing is it
perhaps it has a multi-dimensional
component in other words there's a we
we're in third density
but I sense that it's a fourth density
wave that has third density effect
actually it's much higher than that
dimensionally but it does filter down
through the dimensions and in your
dimension this is the effect you get so
in order to really start getting into
this we have to have a fourth density
DET at least a fourth dimensional or
fifth dimensional
actually understanding of it so that you
can utilize what is happening in your
fourth-dimensional reality right and
would it be would when I've looked at
hyperdimensional physics it it tends to
be that these Quantum leaps and
frequency domains yes so to to get into
the fourth density detection we have to
get to a higher level of frequency yes
and then that gets filtered down into
third density with as like a yes but
you're moving into fourth density do you
understand the difference between
density and dimension yes all right do
all right so you're moving into fourth
density but you will remain in physical
reality in fourth density
the idea is that you already exist in
fourth dimensionality because you have
three dimensions of space and one of
time okay but you need to allow yourself
to begin to understand the properties of
fifth dimensionality to truly understand
from a higher point of view how to
relate to and translate the way in which
these things translate or filter down
into the lower dimensions and go from
your understanding in fifth density so
that you can utilize this understanding
in fourth density and this is why we
urge and encourage all of you to really
work with your higher mind because your
higher mind already exists in the idea
of fifth density so seeing these things
and understanding these things from the
perspective of your higher mind will
allow you greater understanding in your
physical reality experience can we
detect the higher dimensional
frequencies by by looking at the lower
harmonics because I think that we can
you can get hints that they're there
whether you can detect them directly or
not but you can certainly get side
effects that let you know they exist
even if you cannot have a direct
detection okay so that's the starting
point that's the starting point okay
thank you thank you